We
talked about the levels of morality, which means
helping others, the third level, and the second
means generating more good, and the
first
means avoiding harming
others
with your moral behavior, and the
last, the third, is about going around
the
world, and he then says, if you want an
example,
four ways to
treat your students,
and this is the
highest
morality, treating
students, and there are ways to bring them together, and a book by Kapp, if he's already translated, then he also spent 12 years here, which is another 3 pages, and in it, it says, "jimba" means to treat your students with your
generosity,
so super
generous,
so give them good food, my
teacher was very good at that, and that's how
he raised me
too, it
means the student
comes to class and is a dry, hot, moist,
a moist class, to
eat your students,
super generous, B.
We
bought houses, and we also have
one now, the
DRP, who does everything to
support students, that's the first of the
higher morality ways, like you like to
eat, like
your
students like to
study.  and find out and then
put them on like once again honey the bees
on sushi z
what
wasabi okay that good
[music]
tight out
the students like that I have that has
often financially
ruined me we started
in New York when I started with ACI
I had
30 debts when today
000 when I did
diamond courses I
left a big school mountain back then because I had to have all the
food
so don't be
bad karma come back to you but it does
n't happen in a
day but you will never lose money
if you are a student you will
always be happy you will be fine so
if you have to spend money then do
n't worry
dr and
SP have fun
all day partying that's how it should be
second the second point is L your
students
over the green
FL had never had such full students
wow old grandma helped must be that it
's like when you make your
child
mother child
kindergarten
I have harvested
and
see that
yes they do things wrong but
if you when you talk about it
then they are not right sometimes it takes a
very long time until they B  They
do something right, but then just say, "
My student is
okay, no, so I've already given away
all my money again, it's
empty. I
wanted to give more and it's
all gone already."
So great, and encourage them every time they
do something good. Do
n't tolerate it. Don't let
your students do what
they
say. Don't
be lazy, just
keep a low profile
and do what the students say. But then, don't have any
excuses.
If they
do something, then go for it. Make
sure that students
aren't just talking, but also using their... Be a
teacher's teacher. Don't follow what you teach.
So if you're in the teacher's class, if
you don't follow your students' advice yourself,
it's
simply not...
and you
really don't want to do it yourself.
I've had that in my own life.
If you don't follow that, that you don't... Very, very
unpleasant... Then
the
highest... And do
n't...
Work on it, do
Evening TEF... But
then I want to
say things if you don't...
So if
you and your students... Hide...
Very unpleasant...
Then...  Your students won't get that
on
Ken's watch
now
if
you
unconsciously give truthful hints and
others don't
want to
hide anything, it's exhausting, and if you
just sort it out,
your students will know too.
So don't try to hide anything, just make things messy. They're not
perfect.
I'm not saying you have to get
better. Nobody is a perfect
teacher. My teacher is perfect,
but we
all make mistakes. If you stand up and say, "
I am a Buddhist teacher,
and I make mistakes," for
example, I had an abortion when I was very young,
and I honestly admit it,
so the teacher who makes mistakes and
admits them is better than the teacher who acts like
he doesn't make any mistakes at all.
[Music]
He now has an interesting
list. These are different ways
you can or suggestions on how you can
help your students.
Work hard for your
students, and if your students have problems, be
there.
But a student who...
and my wife and I take care of them
personally.
Usually, since people have problems...
So if you
have 128,000 students, you ca
n't
answer everything. So don't go
crazy, but go a lot.  They are
there, and if not,
then
maybe they are especially
attentive to people who aren't doing something they should be
doing. So, if you have a manager in
a
small town who knows how to do things,
then
show a friendly
side and
say you don't know exactly how to help
and always give back
the friendliness someone
has,
then the donation until next time.
Then show your
gratitude to
someone you know who has depression
or is humane.
If you have a lot of students, then
find someone who, above all, cares for
people who have lost
families, have lost
money, have lost their
health, or have lost a home. Then take care of
these people.
The king who
knew no one or
someone is
suffering in a certain way
[music]
has to be busy
and keep them occupied with
their own
moral
code. That's good, so you have to
learn that the next person who has
lost people, people who have lost their homes,
and I,
as a person,
have a
whole [something],
that means
students should take special care of people who, if someone
has lost a home,
then
especially those
where
they are a person, a
mouse, if someone has no place to live.
Even
adopting a cat, unemployed people,
people
stripes, or family
with then a special thing about people
together, have a very
good nose,
not a good nose. If I, a woman,
have to tell me, "You have to take off your shirt, you've had it on for
so long,"
and I say, "I,
I, but if my wife makes a delicious
cake,
but not when it comes to the laundry, but anyway,
the Buddha should have a good nose for
arguments. Argument
times, if there are people in a
Buddhist group who don't get
along well, or
spouses, then Buddha would say,
we would try to help,
or
not. If
sometimes you ca
n't fix other people's problems,
but you can
try, your responsibility
is to try your best. You can't
change anything,
then there wouldn't be any deaths,
because the Buddha was there and the Buddha could
n't
prevent suffering. If the Buddha could,
but it's your
responsibility, don't be discouraged,
you try, try, try,
and if people separate
or there's still trouble in the
Buddhist group, then all
you
can do is simply do your
best. If someone has a problem, I can...
Helping? No, okay.
If you see someone doing something
cool, then try to
support them.
[Music]
House,
garden,
must, must, house,
then the
things,
Scheller,
has, so you can keep
your
house in
order. So, my friend
who
hired me did everything,
and she has a
card that says
everything, every
week.
[Music]
Or, already, a get-
together, gladly,
come, thank you very much to whoever
organized this.
Okay,
people
and one
thing, but if it
helps,
help, if
you have the
opposite, difficulties,
personality, that I, people, not,
I want, people, themselves, people, keep going,
and still, not, my,
always, friendly, like,
who, no
matter if you are a teacher or whatever, but
every person, if you see that
you are doing something that hurts
others,
then say something, so not that
someone else
or something, in a
way, if the
time is over, sweeping
through the sky, lifting a car
with one finger, or
[Music]
paying bills, all,
says, it's an old
Buddhist list, and point 11, if you,
then it's
okay, but just remember, if, that,
you can
move buildings with one finger,
you, DAU, in  If you are in a position to help,
then the
rules are not to
[music]
indicate, but are summarized under the point of
helping others, and it
is interesting that in English,
morality means not killing someone, not
standing, not lying, and in the
Buddhist sense, it is also to do things
for others, to bring them to meditation, to
bring them to freedom, that
is the kind of thing,
even if you don't
want to take the Buddhist one, then at least learn to
see and be familiar with it so as not to
hurt others. If
[music]
to help others, then we call that
morality.
[Music]
have completed the
perfection of an
ethical
life, and we are
now coming to perfection, not to mention it.
Here it means,
but it doesn't mean sitting like
this in the picture, so my friend Vienna, so I'm angry, but I'm not angry, so it's not about him, but about getting upset. [Music] You are, you ...
You
need to go to the toilet and someone is in the toilet at the
restaurant, but it's not up to you if someone else is doing things
all day.
You can then cope and then you
can have a good mood. If
things don't go as
planned, you can have fun
making fun of things.
And I had
a
great car
and
drove down there with it, and then we got
excited. Yeah, we just had that, we just
cleared it away
and had fun.
Someone else, so
that's the essence of
Buddhism, and there are
parts. First, you can
name things, so if someone is wrong,
then someone does something. Second,
you can
be patient with all this
mess
you have. You have
some kind of health
problem.
For example, someone told me I had to have this operation,
and twice I
said I couldn't do it in one go, the
pain had to be endured,
and then I had
another option. It said okay, and that's how it is.
If
you can then take care of yourself,
and if your
pain is the
defining sign, and you have to give way, you don't know.
Nations, because somewhere a
nation comes for free, you have to be nice to
people who
[music] are [ __ ],
second
is to be good even if you have to,
and if we
go to the hospital, then
we
alone already now when we
come and I then have,
why should you
do something like that, no chance anyway, you have to, then
you can also have fun with it, there's no
reason
to be unhappy if you're in
pain, I am, I am just the
first one here, I am the one,
but we all do,
and then you can't avoid it if
you have a period, and then
these things will
happen to you if you have a mother, if you have a
business, if you
have children in a
[music],
all that,
SE,
good, say,
life will be difficult,
just laugh, car, car,
K, or, and
me at
home, and, he or, and, and,
he, cable off, and,
somehow,
just
divide,
once, people, BR,
so,
life is difficult, then, still, good,
booths, you shouldn't, don't, look,
[music],
a child, more, just,
has, that he costs €1000 or whether
he has
won €10000, that,
you shouldn't, dismiss, him  It makes no
difference whether someone wins the lottery
or loses their car, why
should you get upset?
Nobody understands, just heart,
absolutely
beautiful. Should
the
world be free of
one, then three new ones will come
from an old man to young
people? There are a
whole
bunch of [ __ ], and when you were born,
they were all already in a line,
and every year they come, and
new ones keep coming, and your
death, anything is possible. You can
throw yourself out of the house, you can
try to get them out of your
country,
but the line never ends.
If you get rid of one from your life,
then there are such
annoying
people. You can
simply do what you can't do. If you don't shower, don't abstain, don't
meditate, try to
eliminate them from your life, you would still never get rid of them.
Therefore, it's more
logical, and
you should get up, so be done with it.
And
these people,
all people, all people,
the
examples of how to deal with it. Okay, okay,
if you
can do something about it, why should you get upset,
and if
you can't do anything, why get upset?
Okay, the bet is called off.
To cover leather, but simply
shoes. You ca
n't get every annoying person out of your system.  stopping the
world does
n't stop all the annoying people
and
then just
your life's
leather
covered shoes
if you
can annoy your eater all your enemies
if you your so
your tendencies
if you get an operation and
say give me
more if you try to stop the big
idiots in the world then m
or
worship and
a which is called
a kind of the
Spanish I ger GI
einusdu
and that is a different
difficult e
can hold the arm up
for years or
sit in an
outside and see how long
you can sit there
but in Buddhism it's like
if you can be with an ass the whole time in the
office or a married woman
maybe an ass
I am an ass because help me
then help to work on my anger so
that I don't get
upset another
picture
okay
bye
a
spit-up white how many
people ask
me how you do that I'm
relaxed
and people say you don't
say anything because my
wife does
n't even betray a minute of your day
someone says
something
my never see again
bye so just
let them go  And so,
alone with that,
but me with, if
someone
then we,
you young
people, had a very productive life,
my
lawyer
should tell us where everything is, and
maybe make a list,
you books
as it, me, when
people complain
and aren't nice and
annoy me, tomorrow I
have to, is, have so much
anxiety, then
when they
then, just do something else,
which through,
we will end this tomorrow, but from
my heart,
this life is
very
beautiful, don't let unhappy people get to you,
just say if they want,
okay, all right, want
now, diamond,
write, your
family, W,
the
celebration, then a glass of water, and if, if, it
escalates,
then that the
glass, say, don't move, there are
shards, don't move, and you clean everything up,
alarm, forgive, so, and the glass,
just change people's focus,
time, a
million
minutes, but